Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Musical Recordings
  - "Voice Studies", 2012 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_374)
    The cassette's label says, "Side A: The Other Side (10:00); Side B: The Other Side (10:00); Azure Carter: Voice; Alan Sondheim: Hasapi; dominion of striations, vocalizations, spews, and vocalizations - and these can occur in any form, writing, tributes, determining vocalization, perfectly in the voice of azure, sub-vocalization or knot, perfectly in the voice of alan, sub-vocalization or knot. vocalizations becomes paramount, i'd add the prerequisites of walking and talking, subvocalizations dominion of striations, vocalizations. spews, and vocalizations - and these can occur in any form, writing, dominion of striations, vocalizations, electronics, vocalizations/song as body indices, breath/rattling/string and skysphere removal and new spheres, new vocalizations, new grit, new organs impacted by the exertions of the movement, the vocalizations were laced with spews, and vocalizations - and these can occur in any form, listen - "
  - Walls, 1984 (Box 15, Audiocassette 267_461, Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Wedding Tape, Undated; cuid30308 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_133)
  - "Zither" Digital Audio Series, 2006-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_121)
  - Zither (Detuned) Absolute Structure / Conversation, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_214)
  - Zither, Glossolalia, Koto, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_269)
  - [Illegible] Experiments, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_259)
  - [Illegible] Fox, A.S. Bill Viola [Illegible] Playing, April, 1975 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_149)
    Note says "Copy?" Some text is illegible.
- Series IV. Film and Video Recordings
  Series IV. Film and Video Recordings includes Sondheim's work as a filmmaker on a variety of film, video, and digital formats. Much of his filmography includes digital avatars that are manipulated with 3D image warping software. He has also shot a large collection of travel and nature photography and videography. This series also includes some work by Sondheim's contemporaries and collaborators, such as Kathy Acker, Guy deBord, Leslie Thornton, and Laurie Anderson. Much of Sondeim's work includes sexual content and nudity, and viewer discretion is advised. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - .1., July, 1970 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_003)
  - 1, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_670)
  - 1st Day Comb., Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_452)
  - 10.24107 Color, Undated (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_473)
  - 1973 Memory, 1990 (Box 8, Vhs 267_718)
  - 2, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_669)
  - 3, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_708)
  - 35mm Master Negatives, 1981 (Box 79, 35mm film reels 267_010, Box 68, Folder 17)
    Includes original label and work order in Box 68.
  - 4, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_668)
  - 4 Films by Greta S.: Futility, Blood Story, MUTE, Hard-Core Home Movie, Undated; Duration: Futility, 09:00, Blood Story, 03:00, MUTE, 14:00, Hard-Core Home Movie, 5:00; Format: Futility, Blood Story, and Mute were filmed on 16 mm, Hard-Core Home Movie was filmed on Super-8. Contains an old phone number and address for Greta S. and an old call number, F311. (Box 8, Vhs 267_713)
  - 6, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_625)
  - 8, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_710)
  - A.S. & M.C. Compilation, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_720)
    The films in the compilation are listed as: Desire of C.R./ Angelina/ Wupatki/ M.C. The Girding C. W. Fruit/ Untitled
  - Abyss, Undated (Box 2, U-matic 267_581, Box 10, Betamax 267_753)
    267_753 is labeled as the master recording.
  - Accupuncture [sic] 2nd gen., Undated (Box Quarantine 1, Half inch video reel 267_796)
  - Additional footage from The Blue Tape, 1974; cuid21359 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_545)
    Additional footage from the Kathy Acker/Alan Sondheim video work "The Blue Tape." The tape is labeled "acker/sondheim satire/part 1."
    Format: EIAJ 1/2" Open Reel Video, Duration: 30 min.
  - Alan Sondheim Selections, 1977-1987 (Box 7, Vhs 267_658)
    The recordings on this tape include "Sister (1981)," "Despair (1987)," "HeinerMullerWerk: Daughter Courage, for play production (1987)," "Cactus (1984)," and "Fold Catastrophe (1977)."
  - Alan Sondheim Assorted Works, 1991-1992; cuid30336 (Box 21, Vhs 267_659)
    The tape's label notes that it was transferred from Hi8 tapes. Recordings on this tape include "Home," "Desert," "South," "Nature of the Universe," "Vail," and "Garden 1-3."
  - AM for Acquisition Only, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_432)
    The tape's label says "AM for Acquisition Only 43'42 RAW 4 Internet"
  - American Raku 2, Undated (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_515)
    The tape's label has a photograph and a signature on it; the signature is illegible.
  - Andy James, John W. Dall, Undated; cuid30327 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_489, Box 68, Folder 16)
    Includes handwritten note in BOx 68.
  - Angelina, 1989 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_019)
  - Angelina and Sorrow, 1990 (Box 8, Vhs 267_718, Box 10, Vhs 267_774, Box 9, Vhs 267_688)
  - Another Worldy by Leslie Thornton with Karen Cinorre and Anouk De Clercq, 1999; Duration: 23 min (Box 10, Vhs 267_767)
  - Antler, May 11, 1993 (Box 4, U-matic 267_602, Box 10, Vhs 267_750, Box 15, Hi8 267_459)
    Duration: 10 min
  - The Appetition of the Body: Phenomenological Video, Undated (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_529)
    The tape's label also says, "AV 3400; 10 min; Black and White with sound; This tape is deliberately low contrast; Body Into Space: Body Differentiated."
  - Arctic Film: The Meta-Documentary on Lake Hazen, Ellesmere Island, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Art Breath Interview with M. Curtis, 1990 (Box 8, Vhs 267_718)
  - Art Tapes and Florence Tape, 1974 (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_469)
  - Assorted "Clean" Works for Application, 1991-1992 (Box 4, U-matic 267_608)
    Videos on this tape include "Home," "Desert," "South," "Nature of the Universe," "Prison," "Garden," and "Deathwish."
  - "Aster" Digital Video Series, 2001-2004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_131)
  - Attempting to Find a Ground in Hudson River Country, NY (Master), 1977 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_532)
    The tape's label also says, "Black and White, EIAJ standard."
  - Aztec Death, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_399, Box 9, Vhs 267_671, Box 8, Vhs 267_721)
  - "Azurerun" and "Azureharness" Digital Video Series, 2006-2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_132)
  - The Beautiful Film, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_392, Box 8, Vhs 267_738, Box 10, Vhs 267_776, Box 9, Vhs 267_695)
    267_392 is labeled as the master recording.
  - Being Done, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_677, Box 16, Hi8 267_411)
    The recording on 267_411 is labeled as "Being Done II."
  - Being Gone, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_677)
  - Beth, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_499)
    The tape's label also says, "Feedback, Original."
  - The Bicycle in the Time of Ronald Reagan, 1980 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_508, 267_534, Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_466, Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_544, Box Quarantine 1, Half inch video reel 267_468)
    267_466, 267_508, and 267_544 are compilation tapes labeled as "3 California Tapes." 267_466's label also says, "EIAJ Black and White Dub; Reverse Wound." 267_468 is a compilation tape labeled "Duplicates."
  - Big Boss, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_621, Box 7, Vhs 267_662, 267_665)
  - Black, Undated; cuid30322 (Box 24, 8mm film reel 267_140)
  - Blind Cut, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_617, Box 7, Vhs 267_661, Box 10, Betamax 267_762)
  - Blizzard, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_399)
  - The Blue Tape Film - Cover Art, 2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_151)
  - Body Room, 1990 (Box 8, Vhs 267_718)
  - "Bop" Digital Video Series, 2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_133)
  - Border, February 8, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_384, Box 8, Vhs 267_721)
    Hi8 tape 267_384 is labeled as the master recording.
  - Breeding, Undated; cuid30335 (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_502)
  - Bruised Heart, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_558, Box 7, Vhs 267_657)
  - Burning Mtn, Undated; cuid30320 (Box 24, 8mm film reel 267_139)
  - Bykert Tape, 1971 (Box Quarantine 1, Half inch video reel 267_800)
    Duration: 30 min
  - Canada Footage, 1992 (Box 16, Hi8 267_402)
  - Cancer, Undated (Box 2, U-matic 267_583, Box 7, Vhs 267_667, Box 16, Hi8 267_390, Box 8, Vhs 267_716)
  - Canyon Cinema - Film Catalog, 2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_155)
  - Car, July, 1970 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_002)
    Format: Super 8 mm
  - Carlton Chase Showreel: Radical Films, Undated (Box 4, U-matic 267_610)
    The label describes, "In the desert, voices come to you from away. At night, they walk the strand: in search of love, in search of food."
  - CB, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_692)
  - Chatter Death, 1992 (Box 1, U-matic 267_554)
  - Chimp for Normal Short by Leslie Thornton, 1999; Duration: 6 min (Box 9, Vhs 267_678)
  - "Chinese Joy Dance Edit", 2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_134)
  - Chrysanthemum, Undated; Duration: 48 min (Box 8, Vhs 267_706, Box 10, Betamax 267_760, Box 16, Hi8 267_394, Box 5, U-matic 267_616)
    267_394 is labeled "Mixed." 267_616 is labeled "Raw Feedback."
  - City of the Dead and The World Exhibitions, 1995; Duration: 76 min (Box 10, Vhs 267_751)
  - City II, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_411)
  - Civilization, December 23, 1993 (Box 3, U-matic 267_599, Box 16, Hi8 267_413, Box 9, Vhs 267_698)
  - Close Shave - Alan Sondheim / Ann Daly, 1993 (Box 1, U-matic 267_563)
  - Coast, 1980 (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_508, Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_466, Box Quarantine 1, Half inch video reel 267_468)
    267_466 and 267_508 are compilation tapes labeled as "3 California Tapes." 267_466's label also says, "EIAJ Black and White Dub; Reverse Wound." 267_468 is a compilation tape labeled "Duplicates."
  - Color Video Master, Undated (16mm film reels 267_020)
  - Comfort, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_395)
    This tape is labeled as the master recording.
  - Compilation Film, circa 1973-1981 (Box 81, 16mm film reels 267_007)
    Original film can label says "1973 Compilation Film; Before Tasmania 1981; Hartford Footage / Laura"
  - Compilation Tape, 1980-1987 (Box 7, Vhs 267_655)
    The recordings on this tape include "Films 1-8," "Sunset Ship (Korean Film)," "She Came In and Out of the Film He Said (1987)," and "Goodbye Film."
  - Compilation Tape, 1991 (Box 10, Vhs 267_766)
    The recordings on this tape include "Tourist Chasm," "Explain," "Algiers," "HC1," "HC2," "6666," "ETC (Desperate Thought)," and "Beautiful Film Minus Bonnie Parker."
  - Conversation, Undated (Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_471)
  - Continent, October 22, 1993 (Box 14, Hi8 267_383, Box 5, U-matic 267_623, Box 8, Vhs 267_716)
  - Cops and Chinese, Undated (Box 7, Vhs 267_665)
  - CP on Square, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_692)
  - Crystal Crescent Beach Project, Undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Dallas Silent Footage, 1987 (Box 79, 16mm film reels 267_017)
  - Daughter Courage, 1987; Duration: 33 min (Box 2, U-matic 267_578, Box 8, Vhs 267_740)
    This recording is meant to accompany Heiner Muller's production of "Description of a Landscape." Created by Alan Sondheim, Denise de la Cerda, and Andy Karp. Videotape duplicates of film master.
  - Daughter Courage Revisited, Undated; Duration: Approx. 20 min (Box 1, U-matic 267_566)
  - Degrade, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_389)
  - Degraded Imagery, 1991 (Box 16, Hi8 267_388, Box 10, Vhs 267_773)
  - Degraded Imagery II, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_436)
    The tape's label also says "Boost audio thru mix in 1st 6 min."
  - Demonstration / Foolishness, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_453)
  - Desert, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Vhs 267_727)
  - The Desire of Clara Rogers, 1990 (Box 10, Vhs 267_774, Box 9, Vhs 267_677, 267_688, Box 8, Vhs 267_718, Box 16, Hi8 267_405)
  - Despair, 1986-1993; Duration: 8 minutes. (Box 1, U-matic 267_557, Box 4, U-matic 267_603, Box 9, Vhs 267_692)
    267_603 is the master recording.
  - Despair/Hideout, Work/Dance, undated (Box 21, Vhs 267_787)
  - Desperate Thought, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_421)
    The tape's label says "1. Desperate Thought Rises to the Surface; 2. Tourist Chasm; 3. My Talk (Explain); 4. Algiers; 5. Holocaust City; 6. H.C.2; 7. 6666; 3 - 7: Desperate Thought"
  - Devour, Undated; Duration: 25 min (Box 10, Betamax 267_758)
  - Diary Work, 1991 (Box 8, Vhs 267_738, Box 10, Vhs 267_776, Box 9, Vhs 267_695, Box 16, Hi8 267_393)
  - Digital Video Archive, 2000-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_156)
  - Digital Videos - 3D Modeling and Avatars, 2004-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_157)
  - Digital Videos - Avi Files, 2004-2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_158)
  - Digital Videos - Flash Files (SWF), 2000-2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_159)
  - Digital Videos - Short Animations, 1997-1999 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_160)
  - Dragon, October 22, 1993 (Box 14, Hi8 267_383, Box 5, U-matic 267_623, Box 8, Vhs 267_716)
  - "Double Cross" - CMX 12, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_588)
    Other labels on the tape say "Lyn Blumenthal Camera Original, Sound Ch #2, Time Code Ch #1; Master."
  - Dread Fable - Erik Knight, Undated (Box 6, U-matic 267_644)
  - "Dreem / Dremm" Digital Video Series, 2006-2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_135)
  - Drug, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_422, Box 10, Vhs 267_750, Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
    Duration: Approx. 8 min
  - E1, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_446)
  - E2, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_454)
  - E3, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_437)
  - E4, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_456)
  - E5, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_409)
  - E6, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_435)
  - E7, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_458)
  - E8, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_460)
  - E9, Undated (Box 15, Hi8 267_448)
  - Edges or Sea to Shining Sea or Revolution of the Gun, 1978; Duration: 55 minutes; Color; Channel 2 mono sound (Box 5, U-matic 267_626)
    Featuring Laura Hayes as Clara, Laurence Hagarty as Paul, Thomas Zummer as Jean, Galen Strezza, Tamara Bowen, and Michael Millenz. Tech by Anna-Marie Preisemoni and Geralyn Donohue. Thanks to Sidewalk (Hartford, Connecticut), ZBS Media (Fort Edward, NY) Bob Bielecki, and U.C.I. Television Studios.
  - El Niño, January, 1999; Region standard is noted as NTSC (Box 8, Vhs 267_715)
  - Electron Microscope, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_485)
  - Electronic Work, October - November, 1993 (Box 8, Vhs 267_717)
  - "Elo" Digital Video Series, 2008-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_136)
  - ETC A3 + AL, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_385)
  - ETC 4 - Mouth Master / Dance III, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_593)
  - ETC - Full Dance, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_594, Box 6, U-matic 267_641)
  - ETC Tape 1, Undated; Duration: 5 minutes (Box 4, U-matic 267_604)
  - ETC Tape 2, Undated (Box 4, U-matic 267_605)
    Videos on this tape include "Postmodern Pobre" Master, "Milking / I Love Goo," "Eyes Burn," "Border," and "Arise."
  - ETC Tape 2, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_620)
    Recordings featured on this tape include "Landskin 1," "Landskin 2," "My Cunt 1," "My Cunt 2," "Want This Hole (Radio Appears)," "Indiana Dunes," "A Flying Scan Production," "Silent Footage (Landscape) 1," and "Silent Footage (Landscape) 2."
  - ETC Tape 3, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_587)
    Videos on this tape include "Accumulative Train Footage," "Masturbation / Radiate (silent)" and "Borders Exist""
  - ETC Tape 4 - Village Square, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_561)
  - ETC Tape 5, Undated (Box 4, U-matic 267_600)
    Videos on this tape include "My Cunt 1 - Master," "Traveling Against Bad Toaster w/ sound" "My Cunt II - unstable, unusable," "Flesh and Bone - Master," "Suck - Master," "Sand Dunes - Master."
  - ETC Tape 6 - El Paso / Juarez, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_560)
    Videos on this tape include "El Paso / Juarez Map w/ Feedback," "Toaster Globe Map," "C.V. EP to Map," and "From Buffer Cycle."
  - ETC Tape 7 - Drift Fault, Undated (Box 7, U-matic 267_653)
    The recordings on this tape include "Drift Fault," "Borders Exist in Order to Create Your Identity," "Organ," "Wet Me," and "Postmodern Depression No?"
  - ETC Tape 8 - Postmodern Pobre, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_555)
  - ETC Tape 10 - Postmodern Pobre, June 16, 1992 (Box 6, U-matic 267_635)
    This tape includes the recordings "Postmodern Pobre," "PM Geographies," "Things Slide Pulverized," and "Alan Sondheim Fast Scan Productions."
  - ETC 2 Tape 12, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_590)
    Other labels on the tape say "Home (Ari and Chris)" and "Reno's Show Opening, 2/6/1989."
  - ETC 2 Tape 13, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_553)
  - Evidence, September 20, 1975 (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_505, Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_537)
    267_505's label says, "Black and White with Sound, 55 min, Dub - Art Metropole"; 267_537's label says, "62 min, Black and White, 12:45-7:30am, w/seward, Ryan assisting at Deulin Studio NYC"
  - Experimental Television Center - Video Descriptions, 2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_161)
  - Explain (Life), Undated (Box 2, U-matic 267_583)
  - Family, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_397, 267_423, Box 10, Vhs 267_775)
  - Family Beneath the Star, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_422, Box 10, Vhs 267_750)
    Duration: 15 min
  - Fashion, Undated (Box 7, U-matic 267_646, Vhs 267_665, Vhs 267_661, Box 10, Betamax 267_755)
  - Fatwa 447 Demo, 1999 (Box 10, Vhs 267_769)
  - Feedback: Ocean Life Tape, Undated (Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_511)
    The tape's label also says, "Alan Sondheim - Pond Water Tending. 20 min; Sony AV Scan; Black and White; Sound: Sine wave encoding onto subharmonics; Body art: Body control of body; The organisms had to be constantly manipulated. Use high contrast. Note: The info that the water had to be tended must be stated before the tape is played."
  - Fever, April, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_427, Box 5, U-matic 267_618, 267_619, Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
    This recording was created by Alan Sondheim and Jodee Brower.
  - Fever II, 1993 (Box 6, U-matic 267_639, 267_641, Box 16, Hi8 267_414, Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
  - Fever III, July 2, 1987 (Box 3, U-matic 267_585)
  - Fever III, April 2, 1993 (Box 4, U-matic 267_612, Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
    Filmed with Jodee Brower at the Experimental Telivision Center
  - Fifty-six, 2005-2006 (Box 22, Sound disc--vinyl 267_802)
  - Film Equipment Receipts, circa 1970-1995 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Film Notes and Scripts, circa 1970-1995 (Box 68, Folder 4, 5, 6)
  - "Floor Dance" Digital Video Series, 2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_137)
  - Florence - European Tape, Undated (Box 20, Half inch video reel 267_488)
  - Flower, Undated (Box 7, Vhs 267_661, Box 10, Betamax 267_755)
  - Fly Master / Sauge Vitality, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_416)
  - Fold Catastrophe, August 6, 1978 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_027, Box 2, U-matic 267_575, 267_571)
  - Found Footage, 1950-1984 (Box 79, 8mm film reel 267_001)
    Label on original can says "0. Washington D.C. 1950; 1. 1950 found footage; 2. Corporate film '84?"
  - Fractal Mothers, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_591)
  - Frame, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_623)
  - Fucking Myself, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_698)
  - Fun and Games - Makeup, Undated (Box 3, U-matic 267_595)
    Other labels on the tape say "Nikuko Sub-Master, Bad Sync, 12/7/1999" and "The Experimental Television Center, Owego NY." These labels have been crossed out.
  - G-rated, undated (Box 21, Vhs 267_782)
  - Georgian Bay, Undated (Box 81, 16mm film reels 267_028)
  - Geyser, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_422, Box 10, Vhs 267_750)
    Duration: 16 min
  - Godscape, 1991 (Box 7, Vhs 267_665, Box 9, Vhs 267_694)
  - Gouge, October 22, 1993 (Box 14, Hi8 267_383, Box 5, U-matic 267_623, Box 8, Vhs 267_716)
  - Graves (El Paso), Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_399)
  - Greatest Hits, Undated; Duration: 1:58:00 (Box 8, Vhs 267_735)
  - Greatest Hits, 1991; Duration: 1:58:00 (Box 8, Vhs 267_724)
  - Greatest Hits / Duplication Tape II, November 25, 1991 (Box 16, Hi8 267_401)
    The tape's label also says "PCM out; 57 min"
  - Greatest Hits From 8mm, Undated; Duration: 01:57:00; noted as "Mono" (Box 8, Vhs 267_712)
  - Greatest Hits HiFi From 8mm, Undated; Duration: 01:57:00 (Box 8, Vhs 267_709)
  - Greatest Hits Revised, January 29, 1992 (Box 14, Hi8 267_381, Box 8, Vhs 267_733)
  - Guadalupe, Undated (Box 8, Vhs 267_721)
  - Hifi Master II, Including "Desperate Thought" Etc., Undated (Box 7, Vhs 267_663)
  - Heaven, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_398, Box 9, Vhs 267_692)
  - Here and There Last Take, 1976 (Box Quarantine 1, Half inch video reel 267_798)
  - HIOEOUD Work, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_556)
  - Hole, December 21, 1993 (Box 4, U-matic 267_609, Box 5, U-matic 267_623, Box 6, U-matic 267_642, Box 16, Hi8 267_391, 267_420, Box 9, Vhs 267_699, 267_704)
  - Hollywood, 1981 (Reel mss267_container6, 16mm film reels 267_011, Box 2, U-matic 267_573, 267_577, 16mm film reels 267_012)
  - Home, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Vhs 267_727)
  - Hostage, 1981 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_543)
    267_543 is a compilation tape labeled "7 California Tapes."
  - I Agree, 1990 (Box 8, Vhs 267_718)
  - I Am Talking to You: Interviews From El Paso About the World, Undated (Box 4, U-matic 267_611, Box 6, U-matic 267_640, Box 15, Hi8 267_451)
  - I Don't Know I Wanted to Go Back East But, 1980 (Box 18, Half inch video reel 267_551, 267_544, Box 17, Half inch video reel 267_508, Box 19, Half inch video reel 267_466, Box Quarantine 1, Half inch video reel 267_468)
  - I Just Fuck Myself, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_413)
  - I Love You Amy Fisher, Undated (Box 1, U-matic 267_564, Box 9, Vhs 267_696, 267_692)
    267_564 is labeled as the master recording.
  - I've Got Fever, 1993 (Box 8, Vhs 267_734)
  - Ice Phantom, Undated (Box 4, U-matic 267_606, Box 9, Vhs 267_696)
  - Ice Phantom / Spectral Programs, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_424)
    The tape's label says "Ice Phantom 16'50 approx NR2; Spectral Programs 16' approx NR3; Master"
  - Imperilled, Undated (Box 5, U-matic 267_624, Box 10, Vhs 267_752)
  - Internet, May 10, 1995; Duration: Approx. 38 min (Box 7, U-matic 267_645)
  - Interruption, Undated (Box 9, Vhs 267_698, Box 16, Hi8 267_398)
  - Into the European Mirror, 1994; Duration: 56 min (Box 8, Vhs 267_728)
  - Island, Undated (Box 2, U-matic 267_583, Box 7, Vhs 267_667, Box 16, Hi8 267_390, Box 8, Vhs 267_716, Box 10, Betamax 267_760)
  - Japan, August, 1979; Duration: Approx. 55 min (Box 2, U-matic 267_579, 267_572)
    267_579's label says, "Duplicate, without time base correction. With Alan Sondheim, Laura Hayes. Produced at Monte-Video Hartford Connecticut, John Hyjek Camera and Tech. Produced and directed by Alan Sondheim, August 1979. Screenings at Montevideo Franklin Furnace NYC Real Art Ways, Hartford." It also has an address to Sondheim's office at UCLA. 267_572's label says, "For Grant Application. This videotape is similar to my current films; the latter are masterprints only, and can only be rarely projected. Shown at: Museum of Modern Art, New York City; American Center, Paris; Kitchen, New York City. Distributed by: Art Metropole, Toronto, Canada."
  - Je Suis Sage by Kimberly Bartosik with Frederic Gafner, Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_742)
    This tape includes versions with and without subtitles. Unclear whether the subtitles are in English or in French.
  - Jennifer, February 28, 1997 (Box 16, Hi8 267_386)
  - Jennifer, Where Are You? Leslie Thornton, 1981; Duration: 10 minutes (Box 21, Vhs 267_783)
  - Jerome (Everything), Undated (Box 10, Vhs 267_745)
  - Joanna Films - 1st 3 Dailywork Transfers, Undated (Box 16, Hi8 267_418, Box 7, Vhs 267_656)
  - Joanne, 1993 (Box 16, Hi8 267_405)